Guide to the World Student Christian Federation Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- F (a) China, Series L
  - F(a)500 Organized Lines of Work and Study. Religious Departments and Meetings. General Methods
    - F(a)550 Social study and service. Community welfare work, religious and philanthropic, outside of student body
      - F(a)554 Social service. Obligations as to community service implied in Christianity and resting upon the Church
        - Brockman. The Future of China*, 1911 (Box 219, Folder 1675)
      - F(a)556Social morality
        - F(a)556.2Sex education
          - Hall. Sex Education Series* (3 vols.), 1915 (Box 219, Folder 1675)
    - F(a)560 Entertainment. Athletics. Hygiene (see also F(a)514)
      - McCloy. Graded Apparatus Exercises*, 1916 (Box 219, Folder 1676)
      - McCloy. Gymnastic Nomenclature*, 1916 (Box 219, Folder 1676)
      - Tsu. Home Hygiene*, 1920 (Box 219, Folder 1676)
      - Woo. Five Kinds of Exercise for Busy Men*, 1914 (Box 219, Folder 1677)
      - Gulick. Ten Minutes of Exercise for Busy Men*, 1903 (Box 219, Folder 1677)
      - Zia. How to Keep Healthy*, 1911 (Box 219, Folder 1677)
      - Blackie. Physical Culture*, 1910 (Box 219, Folder 1677)
      - Robertson. The Gyroscope and Its Uses (Box 219, Folder 1677)
      - Rules for Volleyball and Track and Field (Box 219, Folder 1677)
      - Many pamphlets re. hygiene* (Box 219, Folder 1677a)
    - F(a)570Business and publicity. Appeals for financial aid
      - Leonard. The Finances of the Student YMCA*, 1914 (Box 220, Folder 1678)
    - F(a)580 Information. Employment Bureaus. Handbooks of university information for new students
      - List of Association Terms, 1908 (Box 220, Folder 1678)
  - F(a)600 Associations in Individual Institutions or among Special Classes of Students
    - F(a)610 Colleges, universities and student departments of metropolitan and state associations
      - General
        - Picture postcards of St. John's University, n.d. (Box 220, Folder 1679)
      - F(a)611 Objects and field
        - YMCA of St. John's University, n.d. (Box 220, Folder 1679)
      - F(a)612 Buildings and rooms
        - YMCA building at Tientsin, 1909 (Box 220, Folder 1679)
      - F(a)613 Organization, incorporation
        - F(a)613.1 Constitution
          - YMCA of Tientsin, n.d. (Box 220, Folder 1679)
      - F(a)615 Organized lines of work and study. Religious departments and meetings. General methods
        - F(a)615.1 Evangelistic and philanthropic work among students
          - F(a)615.104 Meetings, announcements
            - Program for benefit concert for Free Day School at Zaukaido, 1912 (Box 220, Folder 1680)
          - F(a)615.12 Personal work texts
            - Eddy. What is Christianity?*, 1914 (Box 220, Folder 1680)
        - F(a)615.3 Bible study
          - F(a)615.32 Textbooks
            - Burgess. The Life of Jesus and Present Day Problems, 1914 (Box 220, Folder 1680)
        - F(a)615.4 Mission study and service
          - YMCA application materials, n.d. (Box 220, Folder 1680)
        - F(a)615.6 Entertainment. Athletics. Hygiene
          - Cholera chart, n.d. (Box 220, Folder 1680)
          - YMCA Information Bureau material, n.d. (Box 220, Folder 1680)
      - F(a)619 History
        - F(a)619.1 Reports
          - Shanghai YMCA, 1908, 1909, 1914, 1921 (Box 220, Folder 1681)
          - Tientsin YMCA, 1901, 1909, 1913 (Box 220, Folder 1682)
          - Hongkong YMCA, 19091910 (Box 220, Folder 1683)
          - S.J.U., YMCA school*, n.d. (Box 220, Folder 1683)
        - F(a)619.5 Periodicals
          - S.J.U., YMCA school publication, n.d. (Box 220, Folder 1684)
          - Shanghai Young Men, 1917-1918 (Box 220, Folder 1684)
    - F(a)690 Foreign
      - F(a)699 History
        - F(a)699.1 Reports
          - European YMCA of Hong Kong, 1910 (Box 220, Folder 1684)
  - F(a)700 Student Life in General Outside the Federation
    - F(a)702 University catalogues. Educational bulletins
      - Pratiques des Examens Militaires/Examens LittÉraires, 1897, 1896 (Box 220, Folder 1685)
      - West China Union University catalogue, 1919 (Box 220, Folder 1686)
      - Parker. Knowledge vs. Ignorance, n.d. (Box 220, Folder 1686)
      - News items re. education in China, n.d. (Box 220, Folder 1686)
      - Charts of Canton College Hall study for Academy College at TungCho, n.d. (Box 220, Folder 1687)
    - F(a)710 Objects and field
      - Chinese Boy Scouts policy, organization and rules, 1915 (Box 220, Folder 1688)
    - F(a)730 Organization, incorporation
      - F(a)731 Constitution and membership
        - World's Chinese Students' Federation rules, regulations and bylaws; invitation, 1905 (Box 220, Folder 1688)
    - F(a)750 Organized lines of work and study. Religious departments and meetings. General methods
      - F(a)754 Mission study and service
        - General
          - Prospectus of Tsehchowfu Mission, n.d. (Box 220, Folder 1688)
        - F(a)754.7 Education, secular and religious, of natives in mission lands
          - General
            - Canton Christian College catalogue, 1917-1918 (Box 221, Folder 1689)
            - Methodist Missionary Peking University catalogue, n.d. (Box 221, Folder 1689)
            - Hangchow Christian College catalogue, 1917, 1918 (Box 221, Folder 1690)
            - Shanghai American School prospectus, 1916-1917 (Box 221, Folder 1691)
            - Nanking University Constitution, n.d. (Box 221, Folder 1691)
          - F(a)754.71 For the ministry
            - Nanking Theological Seminary bulletin, 1916-1917 (Box 221, Folder 1691)
          - F(a)754.72 Medical
            - Moukden Medical College annual statement, 1916 (Box 221, Folder 1692)
      - F(a)755 Social study and service
        - F(a)755.5 Institutions and organizations for social effort on behalf of students
          - World's Chinese Student Federation Night School in Shanghai, n.d. (Box 221, Folder 1692)
    - F(a)790 History
      - F(a)791 Reports
        - Moukden Medical College, 1917 (Box 221, Folder 1693)
        - Glad Tidings of Peace report of Christian Literature Society for China, 1915-1926 (Box 221, Folder 1693)
      - F(a)795 Periodicals
        - South China Alliance Tidings, 1914 (Box 221, Folder 1694)
        - University of Nanking Magazine, 1919 (Box 221, Folder 1694)
  - F(a)800 Correspondence
    - F(a)801 John Mott w/
      - YMCA associations/American Board Society persons (letters of invitation)*, n.d. (Box 221, Folder 1694a)
    - F(a)810 Ruth Rouse w/
      - Grace Coppock, 1911-1921 (Box 221, Folder 1695)
      - Henry Hodgkin, 1920-1924 (Box 221, Folder 1696)
      - Estelle Paddock, 1908-1914 (Box 221, Folder 1696)
      - Anne Seesholtz, 1920 (Box 221, Folder 1698)
      - Philippe de Vargas, 1916 (Box 221, Folder 1699)
      - Ingeborg Wikander (see also D(b/k)810), 1915-1927 (Box 221, Folder 1.7001701E7)
  - F(a)900 History
    - General
      - Short History of the WSCF*, 1921 (Box 221, Folder 1702)
      - Outline of WSCF history*, n.d. (Box 221, Folder 1702)
      - Lyon. The First Quarter Century of the YMCA in China, 1920 (Box 221, Folder 1702)
      - Lyon. Correspondence re. Tientsin as YMCA headquarters, 1895 (Box 221, Folder 1703)
      - Wikander. Studier Och Bilder Fran Det Nya Kina, 1922 (Box 221a, Folder 1703a)
      - Reports from Chinese YWCA workers, 1911, 19191926 (Box 221a, Folder 1703b)
      - Reports from G.S. Eddy and T. Tatlow, 19201922 (Box 221a, Folder 1703c)
      - Various reports on China, 19201923 (Box 221a, Folder 1703)
      - Reports re. conferences, 19201924 (Box 221a, Folder 1703e)
      - Yen. New Citizens for China, 1929 (Box 301, Folder 2796)
      - The YMCA and the Future of China, 1926 (Box 301, Folder 2796)
      - Letter from Chen Zhongyu on letterhead of Fukien Christian Student Union Leadership Committee, 1949 (Box 316, Folder 6)
    - F(a)910 Reports
      - General
        - Lyon. Encouraging facts re. YMCA work in China, 1906 (Box 221, Folder 1704)
        - Brockman. Materials re. situation in China having bearing on YMCA, 1906 (Box 221, Folder 1705)
        - YMCA annual reports, 1903-1916 (Box 222, Folder 1.7061707E7)
        - YMCA annual reports, 1917-1922 (Box 302, Folder 2799-2800)
        - YWCA annual reports, 1915 (Box 222, Folder 1708)
        - Koo. AntiChristian Movement in China, 1925 (Box 222, Folder 1709)
        - Seescholtz. Student Work of the YWCA of China, 1920 (Box 222, Folder 1709)
        - A Statement on the Tsinan Incident, 1928 (Box 301, Folder 2797)
        - YMCA Activities, 1913, 1925, n.d. (Box 301, Folder 2798)
      - F(a)911 Reports of progress
        - General
          - YWCA reports, 1915-1929 (Box 222, Folder 1709a)
          - YMCA and YWCA reports, 1918 (Box 302, Folder 2801)
          - YMCA Yearbooks, 1931, 1935 (Box 302, Folder 2802)
          - Present Day China (YMCA/YWCA), 1927 (Box 222, Folder 1710)
          - Christianity and the Students of Peking, report of Peking Christian Student Union, 1920-1921 (Box 222, Folder 1710)
        - F(a)911.1 Directories
          - YMCA directory card, n.d. (Box 222, Folder 1710)
      - F(a)912 General Committee Minutes and Documents
        - Hersey. Report for YMCA, Tientsin, 1917 (Box 222, Folder 1711)
        - Lockwood. Report for YMCA, Canton, 1919 (Box 222, Folder 1711)
        - Rugh. General YMCA report, 1919 (Box 222, Folder 1711)
        - Reports of L. Hwang, WSCF delegate to Versailles Conference*, 1900 (Box 222, Folder 1712)
        - YMCA. An Interpretation of Our Present Student Work, 1925 (Box 222, Folder 1713)
        - The Student Work of the YMCA, 1922 (Box 222, Folder 1713)
    - F(a)920 Biography in general
      - Thayer. From Pioneer Home to White House*, 1919 (Box 222, Folder 1714)
      - Woo. The Life of H.L. Zia*, 1917 (Box 222, Folder 1714)
      - Article re. H.L. Zia, 1917 (Box 222, Folder 1714)
      - Zia. Lives of Prominent Chinese Pastors*, 1916 (Box 222, Folder 1715)
      - Zia. The Life of Sir George Williams*, 1914 (Box 222, Folder 1715)
      - Zia. World Leaders*, 1912 (Box 222, Folder 1715)
    - F(a)950 Periodicals
      - Special Bulletin, n.d. (Box 223, Folder 1716)
      - Bulletin of the National Christian Council, 1925 (Box 223, Folder 1717)
      - China's Young Men, 1913-1914 (Box 302, Folder 2803)
      - The Chinese Christian Student, 1926 Nov (Box 302, Folder 2804)
      - Shanghai Young Men, 1913 Sep (Box 302, Folder 2804)
      - Student Bulletin, 1919 Oct (Box 302, Folder 2804)
      - Tientsin Y's Men's Club Quarterly, 1934 Apr (Box 302, Folder 2804)
      - Tung Kung, 1929-1930 (Box 302, Folder 2805)
      - Yale-in-China, 1944 (Box 302, Folder 2806)
      - Articles, reprints: China and the Federation, reprinted from The Student World, 1922 Jan (Box 302, Folder 2807)
      - Miscellaneous publications: Tientsin British Committee of Information, Memorandum No. 28, 1929 Oct 15 (Box 302, Folder 2808)
    - F(a)960 Conventions and conferences, educational and legislative
      - General
        - Reports of various YMCA conferences, 1909-1919 (Box 223, Folder 1718)
        - Student Work Commission report, 1923 (Box 223, Folder 1719)
        - YWCA secretaries' conference*, 1919 (Box 223, Folder 1719)
        - Agenda for student summer conferences, 1923 (Box 223, Folder 1719)
        - Topics for discussion after WSCF Peking conference, 1922 (Box 223, Folder 1719)
        - Zia. The Student Conference*, 1912 (Box 223, Folder 1720)
        - Chinese Student Conferences, 1921 (Box 223, Folder 1720)
        - Poster re. 1922 Peking Conference (Box OV7)
        - Chinese Summer Conference, 1915 (Box 302, Folder 2809)
        - 2nd Conference of Employed Officers of the YMCA of China, 1915 (Box 302, Folder 2809)
      - F(a)960.1 Bibliographies about countries where the convention is held
        - YMCA Kiang Nan Summer Conference, 1905 (Box 223, Folder 1721)
        - Christianity and National Progress, conference of Government School students, 1912 (Box 223, Folder 1721)
        - Student summer conference at Kiukiang and Wo Fo Ssu, 1912 (Box 223, Folder 1721)
      - F(a)960.3 Handbooks, guides, directories, daily bulletins
        - Summer conference handbooks*, 1921, 1923 (Box 223, Folder 1722)
      - F(a)960.8 Announcements and circulars of information and circular letters
        - General
          - Announcements of various YMCA conferences, 1921 (Box 223, Folder 1723)
        - F(a)960.13 Calls to prayer, prayer cycles, song and prayer books
          - Calls to prayer for various YWCA conferences, 1918-1920 (Box 223, Folder 1724)
          - Hymnal for YWCA conferences, 1919 (Box 223, Folder 1724)
          - Meditation and prayer cycle: For the Lord's Remembrance in China (Student Evangelistic Mission), 1913 (Box 302, Folder 2810)
        - F(a)960.14 Unofficial reports, press notices
          - Student Relief in China, 1937 (Box 223, Folder 1725)
        - F(a)960.17 Miscellaneous
          - Student Work Seminar, Kuling, 1922 (Box 223, Folder 1725)
      - F(a)961 Plenary Conferences
        - Yangtze Valley Student Conference, 1910 (Box 223, Folder 1726)
      - F(a)969 Student Discussion Conferences
        - YMCA secretaries' conference, Shanghai*, 1912 (Box 223, Folder 1726)
        - YMCA/YWCA student secretaries' meeting, 1949 Mar (Box 302, Folder 2812)
        - WSCF conference in Tokyo*, 1907 (Box 223, Folder 1727)
    - F(a)990 Miscellaneous Historical Documents
      - Materials re. Time Investment Club (Box 223, Folder 1728)
      - Pamphlet re. YWCA committee functions, ca.1921 (Box 223, Folder 1729)
      - Various pamphlets, English and Chinese (Box 223, Folder 1730)
      - Chiang Kai-shek. A Philosophy of Action, 1940 (Box 223, Folder 1730a)
      - YMCA topics for Open Forum Discussions, 1923 (Box 223, Folder 1730b)
      - Photograph album re. YMCA service to Japanese soldiers in China, 1905 (Box OVd3)
- F(b) Japan, Series LI
  - F(b)000 General
    - Miscellaneous
      - F(b)011 Publishers' prospectuses, trade lists, announcements
        - Brochure (Box 224, Folder 1731)
    - F(b)020 Statistics and charts showing general affiliations and distribution of students
      - Presentation of the Petition for Religious Liberty in Private Schools, 1899 (Box 224, Folder 1731)
      - Maps showing location of schools and distribution of students in Tokyo and Kandaku (Box OV7)
    - F(b)070 Works by officers and members not directly related to the SCM
      - Ojima. Emperor Meiji's Poems*, 1918-1919 (Box 224, Folder 1731)
  - F(b)100 Objects and Field, Extension and Supervision
    - General
      - List of YMCA and its officers in Japan (Box 224, Folder 1732)
      - Notes of a Dr. Knox re. future of Japanese Christianity, n.d. (Box 224, Folder 1732)
      - Pamphlet re. YWCA, 1920 (Box 224, Folder 1732)
      - Komatsu. What is the YMCA?*, 1919 (Box 224, Folder 1732)
      - What is the YWCA?*, n.d. (Box 224, Folder 1732)
    - F(b)110 Needs
      - The Young Men of the Sunrise Kingdom, 1905(?) (Box 224, Folder 1733)
    - F(b)120 Relationships and polity
      - F(b)123 International
        - Contract between Japanese and North American YMCA, 1911 (Box 224, Folder 1733)
        - Fifth Pacific Area YMCA Older Boys' Camp Conference, 1937 (Box 224, Folder 1733)
  - F(b)200 Buildings and Rooms
    - List of donors for student hostel in Tokyo, 1907 (Box 224, Folder 1734)
  - F(b)300 Organization, Incorporation
    - F(b)310 Constitution and membership
      - Various model constitutions*, 1888 (Box 224, Folder 1735)
      - YMCA constitutions, 1897, 1904 (Box 224, Folder 1736)
      - YMCA constitutions*, 1903, 1912, 1920 (Box 224, Folder 1737)
      - YWCA constitutions, 1913, 1918 (Box 224, Folder 1738)
      - Changes in the constitution of the Men's SCM of Japan, 1921 (Box 302, Folder 2813)
    - F(b)330 Membership
      - F(b)332 Basis
        - Definition of the Evangelical Church, 1909 (Box 224, Folder 1739)
  - F(b)400 Salaried Officers
    - F(b)410 General secretary and assistants
      - F(b)415 Relationships
        - Miller. Social and Public Relationships in Japan (Box 224, Folder 1739)
  - F(b)500 Organized Lines of Work and Study. Religious Departments and Meetings
    - General
      - YMCA Christmas and New Year's Greetings* (Box 224, Folder 1740)
      - Asia Study Fellowship, 1968 (Box 302, Folder 2814)
    - F(b)510 Evangelistic and philanthropic work among students
      - General
        - Fisher. Notes on Moral and Religious Influences Surrounding Younger Students in Japan, 1909 (Box 224, Folder 1740)
      - F(b)512 Personal work texts
        - Items listed in card catalog (Box 224, Folder 1741)
      - F(b)513 Life work in religious callings
        - Mott. Future Leadership of the Church*, 1910 (Box 225, Folder 1742)
      - F(b)515 Deputation work among the colleges
        - The National Student Evangelistic Movement in Japan, 1907 (Box 225, Folder 1742)
    - F(b)520 Devotional and inspirational. The Morning Watch
      - General
        - The Morning Watch*, 1897, 1916 (Box 225, Folder 1743)
        - Mott. The Secret Prayer Life and Bible Study for Personal Spiritual Growth (Box 225, Folder 1744)
      - F(b)522 Days and weeks of prayer
        - General
          - Prayer requests for Mott's visit, 1901 (Box 225, Folder 1745)
          - Universal Day of Prayer for Students*, 1920 (Box 225, Folder 1745)
        - F(b)522.1 Calls to prayer
          - Letter re. Universal Day of Prayer, 1899, 1954 (Box 225, Folder 1745)
          - Card re. YMCA day of prayer, 1902 (Box 225, Folder 1745)
        - F(b)522.2 Prayer cycles, litanies and daily helps
          - YMCA prayer cycles, 1897, 1898 (Box 225, Folder 1746)
          - YWCA prayer topics*, 1917 (Box 225, Folder 1746)
        - F(b)522.3 Song books, religious poetry
          - YMCA hymnal, 1904 (Box 225, Folder 1746)
    - F(b)530 Bible study
      - F(b)532 Textbooks
        - Abe. Studies in Romans*, 1911 (Box 225, Folder 1747)
        - Chiba. The Social Teachings of Jesus*, 1909 (Box 225, Folder 1747)
        - Fisher. Studies in the Life of St. Paul* (Box 225, Folder 1747)
        - Fisher. Studies in the Life of Christ* (Box 225, Folder 1747)
        - Gleason. Studies in the Teaching and Life of Christ, 1910 (Box 225, Folder 1747)
        - Gleason. Studies in the Sermon on the Mount, 1913 (Box 225, Folder 1747)
        - Kashiwai. The Teachings of Christ*, 1919 (Box 225, Folder 1747)
        - Kashiwai. Studies in the Gospel of John* (6 vols.), 1912 (Box 225, Folder 1747)
        - Murray. The Life and Works of Jesus*, 1905 (Box 225, Folder 1747)
        - Turning Points in the Life of Christ* (Box 225, Folder 1747)
        - Fourteen Outline Studies in the Life, Character and Teachings of St. Paul, 1898 (Box 225, Folder 1747)
    - F(b)540 Mission study and service. SVM. YWCA. Foreign departments
      - General
        - Pettee. A Buddhist and a Christian Evangelist in China, 1889 (Box 225, Folder 1748)
        - Letter of report re. SVM meeting, 1901 (Box 225, Folder 1748)
      - F(b)544 Mission service. Obligations as to mission implied in Christianity and resting upon the Church
        - F(b)544.1 Motives of missions
          - Materials re. League of Student Volunteers in Japan, 1901-1903, 1909 (Box 225, Folder 1749)
      - F(b)549 History of the student missionary movement as distinguished from the SCM as a whole
        - F(b)549.2 Biography of missionaries
          - Tokutomi. Life of General Gordon*, 1903 (Box 226, Folder 1750)
    - F(b)550 Social study and service. Community welfare work, religious and philanthropic, outside of student body. Home missions
      - General
        - Kawai. Guide to America*, 1917 (Box 226, Folder 1751)
        - Immunization and Emigration* (Box 226, Folder 1751)
      - F(b)555 Institutions and Organizations for Social Effort
        - An Outline of Social Work in Japan, 1922 (Box 226, Folder 1752)
        - The Japanese YMCA (Box 226, Folder 1752)
      - F(b)556 Social morality
        - F(b)556.2 Sex education
          - Morrow. Health and Sex Problems* (Box 226, Folder 1753)
          - Stall. What a Young Man Ought to Know*, 1905 (Box 226, Folder 1753)
    - F(b)560 Entertainment. Athletics. Hygiene
      - Sargent. Health, Strength and Power*, 1905 (Box 226, Folder 1754)
    - F(b)580 Information
      - Association Map of Tokyo, 1903 (Box 226, Folder 1755)
  - F(b)600 Associations in Individual Institutions or among Special Classes of Students
    - F(b)610 Colleges, universities and student departments of metropolitan and state associations
      - F(b)611 Objects and field, extension and supervision
        - General sketch of student and city YMCA*, 1911 (Box 227, Folder 1756)
        - Notes by Chuai no tomo club, 1897 (Box 227, Folder 1756)
      - F(b)619 History
        - F(b)619.1 Reports
          - Tokyo YMCA*, 1912 (Box 227, Folder 1757)
    - F(b)690 Foreign
      - General
        - Lyon. Chinese Students in Japan, 1906 (Box 227, Folder 1758)
        - Pamphlet re. Chinese students in Japan (Box 227, Folder 1758)
        - Sing. The Chinese Students in Japan, 1900 (Box 227, Folder 1758)
      - F(b)691 Objects and field
        - Mott's notes re. Chinese/Korean students in Japan (Box 227, Folder 1759)
        - Articles re. Chinese students in Japan, 19061908 (Box 227, Folder 1760)
        - Papers, reports, etc. re. Chinese and Korean students in Japan, ca.19061908 (Box 227, Folder 1761)
        - Papers, reports, etc. re. Chinese students in Japan, ca.19061908 (Box 227, Folder 1762)
        - Papers, reports, etc. re. Korean students in Japan, 19071908 (Box 227, Folder 1763)
        - Maps of Chinese students in Tokyo, 1908 (Box 227, Folder 1764)
        - Map of Korean students in Tokyo, 1910 (Box 227, Folder 1765)
        - Rush Work; a publication of the Chinese YMCA in Tokyo, including photos of YMCA workers, c.a. 1908 (Box 227, Folder 1766)
      - F(b)692 Buildings and rooms
        - Programme for opening of Chinese YMCA in Tokyo, 1912 (Box 227, Folder 1767)
      - F(b)699 History
        - General
          - Brief History of Chinese YMCA of Tokyo (Box 227, Folder 1768)
          - Materials re. opening of Chinese YMCA in Tokyo, 1907 (Box 227, Folder 1768)
        - F(b)699.5 Periodicals
          - The Chinese Student in Japan, 1908-1910 (Box 227, Folder 1769)
  - F(b)700 Student Life in General Outside the Federation
    - General
      - History of Meiji Gakuin*, 1917 (Box 227, Folder 1770)
      - Post cards commemorating the fortieth anniversary of Meiji Gakein (Box 227, Folder 1770)
      - Alumni monthly of the Imperial Universities*, 1907 (Box 227, Folder 1771)
      - Papers re. League of Nations Association in Japan, 1925 (Box 227, Folder 1772)
    - F(b)702 University catalogues. Educational bulletins
      - News clippings re. education in Japan, 1896-1899 (Box 227, Folder 1773)
    - F(b)750 Organized lines of work and study. Religious departments and meetings. General methods
      - F(b)751 Evangelistic and philanthropic work among students
        - F(b)751.9 Work for foreign students
          - Mission for Chinese students in Tokyo (Box 227, Folder 1774)
      - F(b)753 Bible study
        - Woodworth. The Bible Movement in Japan, 1895 (Box 227, Folder 1774)
      - F(b)754 Mission study and service
        - F(b)754.7 Education, secular and religious, of natives in mission lands
          - Counsel given by J. Swift to an inquirer re. English teachers (Box 227, Folder 1775)
          - Reference blank for teachers in Japan (Box 227, Folder 1775)
          - Greene. The History of a Christian School (Box 228, Folder 1776)
          - Tucker. St. Paul's College, Tokyo (Box 228, Folder 1776)
          - Materials re. Foreign Education Committee, 1891 (Box 228, Folder 1777)
          - Davis. The Doshisha and its Constitution, 1898 (Box 228, Folder 1778)